# Yen Ting Wu

Software Engineer

a9600125a@gmail.com





My name is YenTing Wu, a self-taught software engineer and a creator. My passion for being a software engineer lies in coming up with brilliant ideas with my colleges and enabling them. I take good care about experience, design and communication.

I am also an open-source collaborator, mainly contribute to React community. I currently work with Chakra UI team to build the doc site and maintain DevRel. I love to collaborate with people coming from different backgrounds but having the same goal - Building a better community.

Outside of programming, I love river trekking, biking in summer and exploring wild hot spring in winter. Nature always inspires me.

#### Projects

#### FoF

A brand new dating app.

Expo React Native Zustand React Query

#### 420

A gallery for me to play with design skills and libraries. Mainly built with THREE.JS and p5.

NextJS Chakra UI THREE

**Procrastination** archive

A productivity app to help me understand how FE, BE and DevOps work together.

NextJS Chakra UI Zustand React Query Node Docker

#### Work Experience

### StarkTech UI Engineer

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Designed and developed a food delivery platform with Expo and GatsbyJS

- Developed a web-based client-side food order system with GatsbyJS
- Developed a mobile-based admin-side system with Expo and React Native

#### Open Source Experience

### Chakra UI Collaborator

Aug 2021 - Present

In Docs & DevRel team

- Developed the site's with new features
  - Recent PR Create Showcase Page
- Transform new features into more readable information to improve docs to make use cases more clearly

#### Stacks

Front End React, Svelte

Back End Node, Gin, PostgresQL, Serverless,

Docker

Mobile Expo, React Native

DevOps Firebase, Droplets, HerokuLanguage Typescript, Javascript, Go

### Education

## **Soochow University**

Business Administration (B.A.) Sep 2015 - Jun 2019

нініні